Make a trustworthy human friend
交一个确定可以信任的人类朋友
妖 (Yao): nonhuman beings that have gained spiritual awareness, usually through cultivation
and reveal your identity as a yao.
并告知你的妖精身份
Open the third mission only after July 3rd (Lunisolar Calendar)
在七月初三之后打开任务三
and complete it with your friend.
和你的朋友一起完成任务三
Is this your second mission?
这就是你的第二个任务？
Yep.
嗯
Seems like you've already completed it, though.
不过这么看来你的任务二已经完成了呀
That's right.
是的
Which means... Xiaohei can stay?
也就是说......小黑可以留在这里啦？
And we can do the missions together! Awesome!
还要一起做任务！好棒啊！
Haha, I'm surprised too.
哈哈，我也没想到
But why does it specify for you to complete it with a human?
不过为什么会特地让你找人类一起完成呢？
Can Xiaobai really do it?
小白可以完成么？
Did the person expect Xiaobai to be a 10-year-old elementary schooler when they designed the mission?
任务设定的时候有没有想到小白是个十岁的小学生呢？
If I can't, you can help Xiaohei out then!
我不行的话，就哥哥来帮小黑呗
They didn't really restrict the number of people.
好像也没有规定人数什么的
We'll see.
到时候就知道了
July 3rd, that's tomorrow.
七月初三，就是明天了
Yeah!
嗯！
Can you transform into human form completely?
小黑能完全变成人形么？
Not yet.
还不行
Then maybe stay your cat form in daily life.
那平时还是保持猫形态吧
People will ask if they see your white hair and cat ears.
你的白发还有猫耳被其他人看到总会问起的
How about wearing a hat?
不可以戴帽子吗？
If that's the case, I'd rather be in cat form.
那还是猫形态比较自在
Didn't the president say we could visit some "form shaper"?
馆长不是说过可以找什么人形师吗？
That's still an external approach.
那毕竟是外物
Spiritual Power
in Another World
I'm sure I can gradually improve with my own hard work.
我还是可以凭借的自己努力慢慢变好的
Compared to full human form, I think you look cuter like this!
我觉得这样比完全的人形可爱呢！
Haha~
哈哈~
Spiritual Power
in Another World
Hello?
喂？
Oh, Shanxin!
山新呀！
I know, but isn't it still early?
我知道啊，这不还早嘛
What? Wait!
啊？等一下！
Yo!
哟！
What brings you here?
你怎么过来啦？
I was worried about you.
怕你出状况啊
You haven't started preparing, have you?
你一定还没准备吧？
No. There's still more than one hour, right?
没啊，不是还有一个多小时么？
I knew it.
我就知道
We can log in early.
可以提早进去的
If I didn't come, we definitely wouldn't be able to log in at the same time.
我不来你肯定赶不上跟我同步登陆
Come on, leave it to me.
来，交给我吧
Alright.
好咧
You didn't bring your console?
你没带你的机器来么？
Nah, four players can log into the same console.
不用啊，一台可以四个人同时玩呢
Come join us, gege!
哥哥也一起玩吧！
Shanxin said it's really fun.
山新说这个可好玩啦
Really? What's it called?
噢？叫什么啊
All Living Creatures!
众生之门！
Oh, that...
这个啊......
You know about it?
哥哥你知道？
Yes, I saw it somewhere. It looks interesting.
嗯，在某个地方看到过，好像有点意思
Join us, then.
那就一起来吧
Xiaohei, you should join us too.
小黑，你也来玩吧
Me?
我？
Fufufu, you've also waited for this for a long time, haven't you?
哼哼哼，你们一定也期待很久了吧？
Do you know what game this is?
你们知道这是什么游戏么？
Do you know how popular it is?
你们知道它有多火爆么？
How the heck did you get this limited edition?!
你们到底是怎么得到限量版的！！
Forget it. Let's dive right in.
算了，我们直接来吧
Each person has a receiver. Put it on first.
一人一个接收器，你们先戴好
It's so light, like an eye mask.
The console needs to be connected to Wi-Fi.
主机要先连接上网络
Setting it to the same lobby...
设定为登录房间统一......
Great, we'll be able to turn on the setting at 9:30.
好嘞，九点半就可以开放设定了
Who are you??
你谁啊？？
You need lie in bed while playing this game.
这游戏要躺在床上玩
Press this side button once you lie down.
躺好后按一下边上这个按键就可以了
I'll explain the rest after we log in.
剩下的进去后再跟你们说
OK!
嗯！
Greetings. Welcome to All Living Creatures.
Please state your username.
Xiaobai.
Please select a race for your character.
There are so many...
Huh? Aren't these all animals?
Correct, this is a special feature of All Living Creatures.
Can I change it after I choose?
Not unless this account is deleted.
Hmm... I'll choose human for now.
Would you like to set a new appearance, or generate one based on your own appearance?
Generate one based on my appearance.
Would you like to change your outfit?
No, this would be fine.
Huh?
A baby chick?
A bird!!!
Shanxin??
Would you like to create a sub-account?
This is a special option based on your unique situation.
Very well. Welcome to All Living Creatures.
Please wait for the game to start at the multiplayer platform.
Gege!
Oh, Xiaohei? You got in as well?
Hm? Fascinating. So cats can play too?
That's something new. I should've brought Huangshou.
Speaking of which...
You both chose to be human, how boring.
I don't know what's gonna happen. What kind of game is this?
It's a virtual reality game.
It can perfectly simulate our senses, striving to create a virtual experience that seems real.
Isn't this a bit too realistic...
So what do we do next?
No idea.
We won't know until the server goes live.
The game didn't reveal anything about its content,
but it sold like crazy solely because of its revolutionary genre.
Which is why the opening of this server caused such a stir!
... You didn't feel it at all?
Not really...
Different hobbies are worlds apart huh.
But now this game is about to unveil its mysteries!
And surprisingly, it allows us to play as different creatures.
I've always wanted to turn into a bird!!!
But flying feels pretty hard...
Is this really a video game?
That's amazing—it feels just like reality.
Yeah, but pain perception is dulled.
How in the world is this achieved?
Welcome to All Living Creatures.
I am your guide to this game, MT.
I will now introduce this game to you.
This game is a brand new open world.
Please explore the gameplay through your adventures
Feels like I've seen them somewhere.
and follow the updates on our official website.
This is their company logo.
There is only one thing that needs to be emphasized before your entry:
the concept of "life" in this game.
This is a rule you must know before you start.
After your character dies, if not healed by resurrection skills in ten seconds,
your character will be deleted.
What? Deleted?
Yes, this game simulates real persons.
Each player can have only have one avatar at any time.
After a character dies and gets deleted, the game will refresh and create a new character.
The new character may reenter the game after a 30-minute cooldown.
Ah... What a severe death punishment.
Please protect yourselves just as you do in real life.
Right?
Uhh... I don't really know.
In addition, you can call out the user interface by saying "open" in your head.
To optimize the gaming experience,
this interface can only be seen by your teammates.
If you don't have any other questions,
you can confirm that you're ready anytime.
You may officially enter the game once it's 10 o'clock.
Huh? Are there no tutorials?
Correct.
Interesting.
Try not to get separated after we log in.
The spawn point will probably be crowded.
It'd be quite dangerous before we get used to the game controls.
Us four are already friends by default.
We can find each other even if we get lost.
The experience bar is beneath your name.
We level up once the bar is filled,
and leveling up lets us gain skill points
required for skills.
And the mission panel. We should be able to accept missions here, though it's empty now.
The shop... nothing much in there for now.
This is the battle assistance system.
We'll only know once we get in.
All set?
Let's get ready to log in.
OK!
Oh right, don't we need to choose a server upon login?
No, all the players in this game are in the same server.
... How exciting that there's no load balancing for this many players.
Then... do we log in now?
Yep, let's log in!
Are we... in the game?
I think so.
Wow...
But why is there not a single person around us?
What's going on...
Hm?
Shanxin, what's wrong?
A new message?
CAN'T BELIEVE I CAN'T TALK IN GAME!!!!!
That makes it all the more realistic. Of course birds can't talk.
Hahahahahahahaha.
Aaaa!!! Typing is so tiring!!!!
I'm so pissed... I'll familiarize myself with the controls first.
It only shows 3 kilometers as of right now...
Which means, we need to explore the world first?
Xiaohei, you don't understand these right? I'll read them for you.
Huh!
Someone's there.
He ran away...
Maybe because of our numbers.
Xiaohei,
do you feel the existence of spirits?
Oh... You're right...
Why are there spirits in a game?
I read about this on the yao forum, which was why I wanted to give the game a try.
It's currently the hottest topic in the forum.
This is a game for yao.
Brought to you by Guodong Subs
Translator: Cloud　First proof: K　Timer, Effect & Encoder: Emily　QC: Wuzimiko
This is a free fansub by fans for fans.
We do not own the copyright. Please support the official channel.